Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down.
I am your center. I am everything that
revolves around this universe. I am it.
I am the core of this universe. You
don't [__] understand this. You
cannot [__] understand this. How can
you [__] understand? You need to
kneel. You need to kneel
to me.
Get down on your knees and le to me. I
am your
nothing else. You are nothing without
me. You're nothing. You're a speck.
You're nothing. You're insignificant.
You're a piece of [__] You're
absolutely worthless.
Heat.
for his godly body.
Now, which God stands before you to tell
you to kneel? Which God stands before
you to tell you to do these things?
Nobody. Nobody stands before you. You
stand before me. Which is why you kneel
to me. You worship me. You worship. You
come here to worship. That's why you're
looking at me cuz you're worshiping me.
I am a god.
I am your god. I'm your god. I'm your
god. I'm your world. I'm your center of
your universe.
If you can't acknowledge that,
go away. Go away. If you think that's
untrue, go away. Step away from me.
Except you can't.
You cannot step away from me cuz you are
addicted to me. You're addicted to God.
You cannot get away from God.
I am the center of your universe. I am
your universe. I am God. I am your God.
I'm your Satan. I'm your everything. I'm
your world. That's why you're here.
Because I am your world. I'm your
everything.
You're looking straight into your God.
You're looking into the eyes of God.
God is angry with you. God is
disappointed with you.
You let God down. Now kneel. Kneel.
Kneel. Kneel. You person.
God can't drink. I don't know. What do
you think? God is some kind of perfect.
No, I am your god. I drink whatever the
[__] I want.
2014.
That's not enough. Give me more light.
Kneel to the king.
Why you so weak? You're so weak. It
makes me angry. Making me angry. You're
so weak. You can't even give me more.
Why are you giving me so little? Give me
more angel.
Give me more.
weak. Why are you so weak? Why are you
so weak? Why are you so weak?
Why are you so [__] weak?
Why? You're so insignificant. Give me
more. Give me more. Your God
more dislikes.
More dislikes. Give me more.
You're so weak. You can only give me
this.
Get out.
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
before your god.
Recognize your god. Heal
now.
Get down on your lowest feet. Here, I'll
show you how to do it. You don't know
how to kneel to me. You know how to
kneel to me?
It's simple. I will show you just so you
can understand what you need to do. You
need to be in the lowest spot you can
ever be. You need to be lower and low.
You need to lay down before me and say
please.
Please
let me have mercy. Say please. Say
please. Say kneel
kneel before me like you worship me like
I'm your god like I'm the center of the
universe.
If you can't
If you can't do that,
how do we define it if our universe is
infinite? Is there even a middle point
at all?
We ask what is at the center of our
universe?
me [__] Now kneel, kneel,
kneel, you [__]
Starting
just by watching me, you acknowledge
this fact. Are we going to cheat with
our very first the size of the
observable universe first depends on the
method we use to observe it and doesn't
it? And then we'll finally know if our
cosmos has a middle that's chewy, hard,
or busy. Right. Not really. Because when
people turn it and infinity has no
center when we try to ask where the big
crunch no surely when no find
expand like a balloon and it won't
deflate like one either. And nor will
the contraction of the universe look
anything like a reverse big bang as you
might expect as this would imply that it
would contract in the center of the
universe or what?
Okay guys,
now I want you to um
take a chill pill. Don't kneel to me,
okay? Just take a chill pill. I want you
to take a chill pill and uh just realize
that um
I might be the center of the universe
because all that revolves revolves
around me and um
I'm not saying that the whole universe.
I'm just saying
you got to put all your hatred on me.
You got to put all your dislikes on me.
You will make sure that I am the center
of the universe. The more attention you
put to me, the more people you put to
me, the more viewers, the more words,
the more everything I can express, the
more you prove to me that I am the
center of the universe and I am. Give me
more. Give me case like you never seen
before. Give me kneeling. Kneel to God,
not like you never kneel before.
But listen to me. Listen to me when I
talk. Everyone has this path and you
need to listen to everyone cuz every
human being has God inside them.
And once you can understand this, once
you understand that you cannot bring
people down because you bring God down.
And when you bring God down, you bring
yourself down. And when you bring
yourself down, you go to hell.
Now, instead of bringing yourself to
hell, you need to bring everyone to God,
you need to go, you need to do good in
this world.
You need to bring everything to the
light.
If you take the darkness and you bring
the darkness to the darkness, you will
be with the Lord. You will be there with
the Lord of the darkness.
That is also me. And I will be in the
end, light, dark, doesn't matter.
But please, this world we live in, this
human nature, this human world we live
in,
bring good to it.
You have one life. You have only one
life. You have one chance. What are you
going to do with this one chance?
What?
I'm talking to you. What are you going
to do with this one chance in life? You
have one chance. It's from your birth
until you die. You have one chance. You
can't redo it. What are you going to do
with it? You're going to bring good to
it.
It's really good. You're going to be
impaired to it. I'll be there to watch
you. I will be right there to watch you
just like the rest of the world. and the
rest of the world will judge you and you
will be brought to pain and suffering.
That's why I ask you, you have this one
chance in life. You have only one chance
in life. You don't have two chances. You
are you were born and then you die.
Everything in between is a chance.
This chance in life,
what are you going to do? You're going
to do the best. You're going to do the
worst. If you do the worst, trust me, I
will be at the end of it. I will bring
you the worst. I will be your Satan. I
will bring your hell. And I will bring
you
forever
eternity of suffering
because I am your God. You need to kneel
before me. You need to kneel before me.
You can't understand that I will be at
the end of your road. I'll be your
suffering. I'll be everything.
I'll be your joy, your suffering,
everything in your life.
If you can't understand it, try and
understand it now. Try and [__]
understand that you have only one life.
You have this life. You maybe have
another life, but you only have this
life. What are you going to use it for?
You going to use it for bad or you going
to use it for good? You use it for bad.
People will come to get you. I will come
to get you.
And not only that, we will tell the
world that you are bad. So, so I ask
you, I ask you, you peasants,
bring something better to life cuz you
have only one chance. You have only one
chance.
I am your god.
You have one chance and I am watching
you.
I know it is [__] Wait, let me get
some real music for you guys because I'm
[__] real. I'm [__] real with you
guys. You only have one chance, right?
And you're misusing that chance. Now
[__] use it for something good.
The life you have, your one life. Now
[__] use it.
Use it.
Put this random [__] on. But I hope it
makes sense what I'm saying to you guys.
I really hope it makes sense. You think
my dad died of sh You think my dad died
of shame?
My dad guides me. My dad is me.
My dad is in the soul of me. My dad
lives inside of me.
You cannot understand that. You cannot
understand God.
If you cannot understand God, so you
shall kneel.
Kneel before me. I'm God in a human
form. If you cannot accept that I burp
and I fart,
then you cannot accept God
from all the energies condensed. I'm in
a human form of God and devil.
I'm not Jesus. I'm not God. I'm not
devil. I'm everything.
I hear the words of God.
I hear God speaking to me.
He's speaking to you through me.
You're listening right now. That's why
I'm God. I am not God in the flesh.
I just speak for him.
I'm here because you never listen.
You never listened in your life. Never
listen to God.
So I'm here to speak for God. What God
tells you is that you need to be doing
things right.
You need to fill your heart with love.
Put it on people. Fill this heart with
love. Fill it up. Fill it up with love.
Once you fill it up with love, you share
it. You give it to people.
When you can give that, that's when
love, that's when God will accept you
into his heart. Worst road you can get.
I'm at the end of all of it. Try and
realize that I am your God.
I'm your God.